filehorse.com 2019-03-09

# Privacy Policy / FileHorse.com

Privacy Policy

At FileHorse we consider the privacy of our visitors to be extremely important. This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information is collected and recorded by FileHorse.com and how this data it is used. No effort is made to identify individuals without their knowledge.

Log Files

Like many other Web sites, FileHorse.om makes use of log files. These files merely logs visitors to the site - usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services's analytics. The information inside the log files includes IP addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

Cookies

FileHorse.com uses cookies to store information about visitors' preferences only in order to improve user experience using our site. User can choose if he wants to accept or reject all the cookies by modifying your browser preferences. It is possible that by rejecting cookies some functions of the site will not function properly.

Ad Networks

We use Google AdSense and they serve ads on our site based on a user's prior visits to our website. Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to our sites and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). Alternatively, users can opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

FileHorse.com may also use other advertising networks (other than Google AdSense), whose privacy policies will always be listed on their respective sites. Most of these companies belong to the Network Advertising Initiative. Our visitors may opt-out of behavioral advertising methods by visiting [networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

Google Analytics

Google Analytics is a free service provided by Google Inc. for gathering statistical information about visitors to a website. This information generally includes IP addresses, geographical location of the IP address, pages visited, how the visitor arrived at the webpage and computer information, such as the operating system and browser used. Google Analytics is implemented through a cookie, which is placed on the visitor's computer coupled with code in the webpage, which collects visitor data and relays it to Google's servers for processing.

Our visitors can opt out of Google Analytics by using the opt-out service provided by Google: [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

Unsolicited Communication

FileHorse.com will not use your e-mail address in order to send you any kind of unsolicited or promotional mail. It is your choice whether you decide to receive newsletters or not from us. You can always choose to unsubscribe from our newsletter services by visiting a link in footer of every email.

Children's Information

We believe it is important to provide added protection for children online. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children to observe, participate in and/or monitor and guide their online activity. FileHorse.com does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian believes that FileHorse.om has in its database the personally identifiable information of a child under the age of 13, please contact us immediately (using the contact form) and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

Consent

By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.

Update

Any changes we may make to our Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on this page and. Users subscribed to our newsletter will be notified by e-mail.
